Ms.		O		4		0.005908419497784343
44		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
years		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
old		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
would		O		5		0.007385524372230428
first		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
woman		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
black		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
head		O		3		0.004431314623338257
five-member		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
commission		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
that		O		3		0.004431314623338257
oversees		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
markets		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
's		O		5		0.007385524372230428
candidacy		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
being		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
championed		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
by		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
several		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
powerful		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
lawmakers		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
including		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
her		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
boss		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Chairman		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
John		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Dingell		PERSON		2		0.0029542097488921715
-LRB-		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
D.		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Mich.		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
-RRB-		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Energy		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Commerce		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Committee		ORGANIZATION		3		0.004431314623338257
She		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
currently		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
counsel		O		4		0.005908419497784343
committee		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Mr.		O		3		0.004431314623338257
have		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
been		O		4		0.005908419497784343
considered		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
allies		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
exchanges		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
while		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
banks		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
futures		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
often		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
fought		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
with		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
them		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
A		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
graduate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Harvard		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Law		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
School		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
worked		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
as		O		6		0.008862629246676515
laywer		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
for		O		15		0.022156573116691284
corporate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
finance		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
division		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
SEC		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
late		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
1970s		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
has		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
congressional		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
since		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
1979		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Separately		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
transition		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
officials		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
said		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Frank		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Newman		PERSON		2		0.0029542097488921715
50		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
vice		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
chairman		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
chief		O		3		0.004431314623338257
financial		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
officer		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
BankAmerica		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Corp.		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
expected		O		7		0.0103397341211226
nominated		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
assistant		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Treasury		ORGANIZATION		4		0.005908419497784343
secretary		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
domestic		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
who		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
giving		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
up		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
job		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
pays		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
$		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
1		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
million		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
year		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
oversee		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
auctions		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
government		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
well		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
banking		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
issues		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
He		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
report		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
directly		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Secretary-designate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Lloyd		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Bentsen		PERSON		2		0.0029542097488921715
headed		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Senate		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
Finance		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
past		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
six		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
also		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
nominate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Samuel		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Sessions		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
tax		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
one		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
top		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
jobs		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
at		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
As		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
early		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
today		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
camp		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
name		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
five		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
undersecretaries		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
state		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
secretaries		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Peter		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Tarnoff		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
former		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Carter		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
official		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
president		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Council		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
on		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Foreign		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Relations		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
named		O		3		0.004431314623338257
undersecretary		O		3		0.004431314623338257
political		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
affairs		O		4		0.005908419497784343
Former		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Sen.		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Tim		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Wirth		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
get		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
newly		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
created		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
post		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
global		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
which		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
include		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
refugees		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
drugs		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
environmental		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Earlier		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Colorado		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Democrat		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
had		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
contender		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Environmental		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Protection		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Agency		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
In		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
addition		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Joan		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Spero		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
executive		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
American		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Express		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Co.		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
economic		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
And		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Time		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
magazine		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
columnist		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Strobe		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Talbott		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
ambassador-at-large		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
coordinate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
U.S.		LOCATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
policy		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
toward		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Soviet		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Union		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
Several		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
appointees		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
President		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Bush		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
are		O		3		0.004431314623338257
likely		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
stay		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
office		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
least		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
temporarily		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
until		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
permanent		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
successors		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
can		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
One		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Bernadine		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Healy		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
director		O		3		0.004431314623338257
National		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Institutes		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Health		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Another		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
holdover		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
David		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Kessler		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Food		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Drug		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Administration		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
offfice		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Trade		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Representative-designate		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Mickey		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Kantor		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
selections		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
three		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
deputy		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
trade		O		3		0.004431314623338257
representative		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
slots		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
general		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
still		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
decided		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
But		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Robert		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Kyle		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
or		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
elsewhere		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
For		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
many		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
subcabinet		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
list		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
candidates		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
narrowed		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
considerably		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
deciding		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
between		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
recently		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
retired		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Rep.		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Matthew		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
McHugh		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
N.Y.		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
activist		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Gus		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Speth		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
International		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
Development		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Among		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
others		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
hired		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Kitty		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Higgins		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
aide		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Michigan		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Sander		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Levin		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
staff		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
Labor		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Department		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Jerry		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Palast		PERSON		1		0.0014771048744460858
Service		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Employees		ORGANIZATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
department		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
legislative		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
incoming		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
seriously		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
considering		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
moving		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
briefing		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
room		O		2		0.0029542097488921715
press		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
decades		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
situated		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
West		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Wing		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
White		ORGANIZATION		2		0.0029542097488921715
out		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
into		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
Old		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Executive		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Office		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
Building		LOCATION		1		0.0014771048744460858
next		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
door		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
The		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
current		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
could		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
used		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
offices		O		1		0.0014771048744460858
